Arabia
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Arabia, 2.1.2.1.1
  - Bedouin family living in Petra Palace, 1918; 12; 1-185; color (Box 1337)
  - Bedouin family living in Petra Palace, 1918; 13; 1-185; b&w (Box 1337)
  - Two Arab men with pistols [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: “Drinkers of the milk of war”], 1918; 14; 1-191; color (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba, Mecca, crowd, fort in distance [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The mosque of the holy Kaaba], 1918; 15; 1-192; color (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba, Mecca, crowd, fort in distance [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The mosque of the holy Kaaba], 1918; 16; 1-192; b&w (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba Mecca, 1918; 17; color (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba Mecca, 1918; 18; color (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba Mecca, 1918; 19; color (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba Mecca, 1918; 20; b&w (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba Mecca, 1918; 21; b&w (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba Mecca, 1918; 22; color (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba Mecca, 1918; 23; color (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba Mecca, 1918; 24; b&w (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba Mecca, 1918; 25; color (Box 1337)
  - Mecca, panorama of city (copy from book), 1918; 26; 1-194; color (Box 1337)
  - Medina (copy from book), 1918; 27; 1-195; color (Box 1337)
  - Holy rock, capy from Zwemer, 1918; 28; 1-197; color (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba, Mecca, distant view, 1918; 29; 1-204A; color (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba, Mecca, distant view, 1918; 30; 1-204A; b&w (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba, Mecca, distant view, 1918; 31; 1-204A; b&w (Box 1337)
  - The Kaaba, Mecca, distant view, 1918; 32; 1-204A; b&w (Box 1337)
  - Dynamited steel bridge, Hedjaz Railway [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: One of the many bridges blown up by Lawrence’s “tulips.”], 1918; 33; 1-205B; color (Box 1337)
  - Map of near East, Petra indicated with big red star, 1918; 34; 1-206; color (Box 1337)
  - Map of near East, Petra indicated with big star, 1918; 35; 1-206; b&w (Box 1337)
  - Map of near East, Petra indicated with big star, 1918; 36; 1-206; b&w (Box 1337)
  Box 1338
- Arabia, 2.1.2.1.1
  - Sunset, Red Sea, silhouette of caravan, 1918; 1; 1-214; 3x4 b&w (Box 1338)
  - Sunset, Red Sea, silhouette of caravan, 1918; 2; 1-214; 3x4 b&w (Box 1338)
  - Panorama of Akaba [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Panorama of Akaba], 1918; 3; 1-220; 3x4 b&w (Box 1338)
  - Panorama of Akaba [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Panorama of Akaba], 1918; 4; 1-220; 3x4 b&w (Box 1338)
  - Panorama of a Bedouin encampment at Akaba [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: A Bedouin encampment], 1918; 5; 1-221; 3x4 b&w (Box 1338)
  - Panorama of a Bedouin encampment at Akaba [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: A Bedouin encampment], 1918; 6; 1-221; 3x4 b&w (Box 1338)
  - Palm trees, man carrying two buckets [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Where the hosts of Israel are said to have terminated the passage of the Red Sea], 1918; 7; 1-222; 3x4 b&w (Box 1338)
  - Palm trees, man carrying two buckets [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Where the hosts of Israel are said to have terminated the passage of the Red Sea], 1918; 8; 1-222; 3x4 b&w (Box 1338)
  - Palm trees, sea, sunset, silhouette of man [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Date-palms along the coral shore of Araby], 1918; 9; 1-223; 3x4 b&w (Box 1338)
  - Palm trees, sea, sunset, silhouette of man [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Date-palms along the coral shore of Araby], 1918; 10; 1-223; 3x4 b&w (Box 1338)
  - Man sits on kneeling camel, 1918; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1338)
  - The salt lagoon in Jezirat Faraun, Akaba, 1918; 12; 3.25x3.25 b&w (Box 1338)
  - The salt lagoon in Jezirat Faraun, Akaba, 1918; 13; 3.25x3.25 b&w (Box 1338)
  - Auda Abu Tayi, 1918; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1338)
  - Three people and camels in the Arabian desert, 1918; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1338)
  - Three people and camels in the Arabian desert, 1918; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1338)